(Sheldon:)...you expect me to plunk down
thousands of dollars.
(Assistant:)Actually, that's only 750.
Everything's on sale.
Really? Talk to me
about that pocket watch.
(Howard:)I'm still trying to wrap
my mind around it.
(Howard:)I always thought
I'd be a dad someday.
(Raj:)Me too. You're so caring.
(Raj:)I've often pictured you guiding
a young boy into manhood.
(Leonard:)There you go, Howard. Sounds like Raj'll
have your babies. Problem solved.
(Raj:)Because a man
shows caring for another man...
(Raj:)...doesn't mean he's displaying the love
that dare not speak its name.
Did she say she didn't want kids?
(Howard:)Yeah. She doesn't like them.
(Howard:)And from what I saw,
the feeling was mutual.
- What are you gonna do?
- I don't know.
(Howard:)I can't see a life where I don't have kids.
I mean, people have kids.